Zaw Myo Latt

Back-end Developer

Address – Blk 93, #04-3037, Paya Lebar Road, Singapore 370093.

Mobile - +6587847812, Email - zawmyolatt.ucsy@gmail.com

Linkedin – https://www.linkedin.com/in/zaw-myo-latt-57449979

Skype – zawmyolatt1122

Summary

My name is Zaw Myo.Graduated from the University of Computer Studies, Yangon (UCSY) in Myanmar and got a Bachelor of Science in Computer Information and Technology (B.C.Sc). Experiences and knowledge obtained through university life and work experiences. After graduating from university, I have an interest in web application area. That's why I worked as a web developer for over 1 year. Then, i was promoted as a Team Leader at the same company iKloudit Myanmar Office (iKloudit is a Singapore Company), locally called Ever Crystal One-stop IT Solution. There, we have to write the web app projects, which were sold in our Singapore Head Office such as HR System, POS System, CMS and other E-commerce System etc,.

Then after 3 years, I joined <u>GMBF Group of Companies</u> (which was founded myanmar) as an IT Manager.In GMBF, i took the responsibility of project management, task management, mobile apps and web apps development like Bus Ticket Booking system, Coupon based marketing development system etc. After 2 years later, I moved to Singapore at Feb 2019 and joined as Back-End Developer in <u>Carpal Fleet</u>. And at the sametime, I founded a freelance software company in Myanmar with a friend at 2017, called <u>Pro-X Software Solution</u>. That also developing many software development services for many platforms.

Educational Background

Bachelor's Degree of Computer Science/Information Technology

Major: **Software Engineering**

Institute/University: University of Computer Studies, Yangon, Myanmar

Current Specialization: Web Technology – Web Application – Back-end Services

Graduated Date: May 2013

Honors and Certificates

2010-2011 - Durosoft Web Studio, Certified in advanced PHP (Now Fairway web)

2011-2012 - Certified in Practical Network Course

- Certified the Excellence in IT Business Plan Contest 2013(ICCNA)

- Winner team of Contest on Technopreneurship 2014

(Conducted by Myanmar-Korea IT Center)

Personal Particulars & Preferences

Date of Birth: **12 Jan 1993**

Nationality: **Myanmar**

Experiences

iKloudit (Web Developer)





- Developed web applications by using PHP framework like code igniter/ laravel, etc
- Most of the applications which I developed in there are POS System, Invoicing System, HR System and LMS System etc.



Ever Crystal (Team Lead)

Oct 2015 - 2018

- Developed web applications by using PHP framework like code igniter/ laravel, etc
- Developed web api services and also did integration with some kind of api interface like rest, soap.
- Also develop hybrid mobile application by using ionic1 and angular1,cordova etc
- Most of the applications which I developed in there are Reward System, HR System and Ecommerce System etc.

GMBF Group of Companies (IT Manager)



Nov 2018 - Dec 2019

- Developed web applications by using PHP framework like code igniter/ laravel, etc
- Developed web api services and also did integration with some kind of api interface like rest, soap.
- Did cloud server management, CI/CD and git branching strategy
- Also develop hybrid mobile application by using ionic 3 and angular 2, cordova etc
- Most of the applications which I developed in there are Reward System, HR System, Ecommerce System, Bus Ticketing System and other travel & tour related system.

<u>Carpal Fleet</u> (Back-End Developer)



Jan 2019 - Present

 Developing web application fleet api by using laravel (PHP), python, aws serverless (Lambda), elasticsearch etc.,

Languages

Language	Spoken	Written
Burmese	Native	Native
English	Intermediate	Advance
Tamil	Beginner	-

Communication Skill

I worked together with Singapore Marketing Team to communicate on Skype, since 2014 when i worked at ikloudit. And also in previous companies, I work together with some foreign scrum master, product managing guys as remote.

Additional Basic Knowledge and Skills

- GoLang
- Ruby on Rail
- Android (Java) programming language
- Kotlin
- JQuery Mobile
- Phone gap
- VB language
- Assembly language